<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SUSE World</title><link>https://workadventure-suse.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on SUSE World</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://workadventure-suse.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enter the SUSE Hack Week World!</title><link>https://workadventure-suse.github.io/tutorial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://workadventure-suse.github.io/tutorial/</guid><description>The SUSE Hack Week is not only the time to innovate and grow but also to meet different people inside the company. This time we want to bring the socializing to you in another format: A digital SUSE Hack Week World based on workadventu.re!
Entering the SUSE Hack Week World! By clicking the link below you agree with our privacy policy.
Navigating the world use the arrow keys to navigate around the world use the shift key to run enter the proximity of another player to start a voicechat use the meeting rooms to talk to bigger groups explore the maps and find hidden treasures!</description></item><item><title>Information on Personal Data Processing</title><link>https://workadventure-suse.github.io/legal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://workadventure-suse.github.io/legal/</guid><description>You can download a copy of the document here.
Information on Data Processing for SUSE Hackweek workadventu.re Background You are about to participate in the openSUSE Hackweek Workadventu.re. In order to facilitate your participation and to administer hackweek , SUSE Software Solutions Germany GmbH and its corporate affiliates (“SUSE Group”) must process certain personal data which you provide (“Personal Data”).
Controller The controller of the processing for the purposes of Article 4(7) GDPR is SUSE Software Solutions Germany GmbH, Maxfeldstraße 5, 90409 Nuremberg, Germany.</description></item></channel></rss>